https://www.bayfed.com/privacy

Products & ServicesAuto Loans and RefinancingCredit Cards and Debit CardsDeposit, Loan and Credit Card RatesHome Loans and Home Equity Lines of CreditElectronic Services, Online BankingPersonal LoansPersonal Checking AccountsPersonal Savings AccountsBusiness Services and Credit CardsInvestments and RetirementStudent and Youth AccountsImportant Disclosure DocumentsLoan Information Questions and AnswersSkip a Loan PaymentGet the Home of Your Dreams!
Competitive rates on loan amounts up to $3,000,000.
Apply Now!Member BenefitsMember Benefits -
DiscountsMember Benefits - InsuranceAutoSmart Car Market ToolsGet the Home of Your Dreams!
Competitive rates on loan amounts up to $3,000,000.
Apply Now!Advice & PlanningInvestment ServicesFinancial Education ResourcesFraud Prevention and ActionFinancial CalculatorsForeclosure PreventionDecedent Information and ResourcesGet the Home of Your Dreams!
Competitive rates on loan amounts up to $3,000,000.
Apply Now!About UsCOVID-19 Support ResourcesCareers at Bay FederalReal Estate Owned PropertiesLocations, Hours and ATMsDedicated to Community SupportBay Federal Credit Union NewsBay Federal LeadershipFrequently Asked QuestionsAbout Bay Federal Credit UnionOnline Privacy PolicyDevice and System RequirementsBayFedOnline Maintenance ScheduleGet the Home of Your Dreams!
Competitive rates on loan amounts up to $3,000,000.
Apply Now!
Menu
Search
Products & ServicesAuto Loans and RefinancingCredit Cards and Debit CardsDeposit, Loan and Credit Card RatesHome Loans and Home Equity Lines of CreditElectronic Services, Online BankingPersonal LoansPersonal Checking AccountsPersonal Savings AccountsBusiness Services and Credit CardsInvestments and RetirementStudent and Youth AccountsImportant Disclosure DocumentsLoan Information Questions and AnswersSkip a Loan PaymentGet the Home of Your Dreams!
Competitive rates on loan amounts up to $3,000,000.
Apply Now!Member BenefitsMember Benefits -
DiscountsMember Benefits - InsuranceAutoSmart Car Market ToolsGet the Home of Your Dreams!
Competitive rates on loan amounts up to $3,000,000.
Apply Now!Advice & PlanningInvestment ServicesFinancial Education ResourcesFraud Prevention and ActionFinancial CalculatorsForeclosure PreventionDecedent Information and ResourcesGet the Home of Your Dreams!
Competitive rates on loan amounts up to $3,000,000.
Apply Now!About UsCOVID-19 Support ResourcesCareers at Bay FederalReal Estate Owned PropertiesLocations, Hours and ATMsDedicated to Community SupportBay Federal Credit Union NewsBay Federal LeadershipFrequently Asked QuestionsAbout Bay Federal Credit UnionOnline Privacy PolicyDevice and System RequirementsBayFedOnline Maintenance ScheduleGet the Home of Your Dreams!
Competitive rates on loan amounts up to $3,000,000.
Apply Now!
Coronavirus (COVID-19) Health Emergency
Updates and resources during the current health emergency.
Learn more
Helpful Resources
Lost or Stolen Card?
Current Rates
ATM Locations
Membership
Consumer Fee-Schedule
Important Disclosures
Privacy
Privacy
Member Privacy Information
Bay Federal takes your privacy and personal information very seriously. We have a dedicated group of information security and compliance professionals that work tirelessly to ensure that we stay on top of the latest state and federal guidelines, and that we are protecting all of our information systems.
Our policies thoroughly and transparently outline how your data is used, both in regards to our online services and your sensitive member information. Below you will find information related to these policies. To the right, you may request to limit the information that Bay Federal shares with third parties for marketing purposes, as outlined in our Federal Privacy Notice and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) Disclosure.
Protect Your Information
Bay Federal will never contact you directly and request sensitive private information (i.e., your account number, your social security number, etc.). Any time we need to collect or update your information, we will point you towards a secured site with your own established login credentials, such as online banking.
If you receive a request to provide specific account information from someone claiming to represent Bay Federal, do not share that information and please contact us immediately.
Privacy Notice
Our federal Privacy Notice outlines how Bay Federal may use and/or share your information. You may opt out of information sharing to third parties for marketing purposes by filling out the form to the right, or by following instructions in the Privacy Notice.
California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA)
Under the CCPA, residents of California have additional rights pertaining to their personal information and privacy. Our CCPA Disclosure further outlines how Bay Federal Credit Union may collect, share, use, and protect your information.
Online Privacy Policy
Bay Federal Credit Union is committed to implementing appropriate protections for any personal information that we collect or our users share with us. Our Online Privacy Policy outlines how Bay Federal may collect, use, and/or share any of your information obtained through the use of our website or online services.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) prohibits unfair or deceptive acts or practices in collection, use, or disclosure of personally-identifiable information from or about children under the age of 13 on the internet. Our COPPA Policy describes why, when, and what personally-identifiable information Bay Federal may collect about children through our website.
Requests to Know, Opt-Out of Data Sharing, or Requests to Delete Information
You have the right to know the information we request, the right to opt-out of data sharing, as well as the right to request deletion of your information. You may do so by:
Completing the online form that accompanies this page.
Requesting the information in person at any branch location.
By calling us at 831.479.6000 or toll-free at 888.4BAYFED, extension 3.
By writing to the Credit Union with the request. Written requests may be mailed to:
Your Name:
Click to add
(?)
Your Member Number:
Click to add
(?)
Your Email Address:
Click to add
(?)
Your Daytime Phone Number:
Click to add
(?)
Submitting this form limits Bay Federal sharing your information for marketing purposes. Review our Privacy Notice for more information.
Generate New Image
Type the code from the image
Bay Federal at your fingertips. Download our mobile apps for iPhone and Android now!
